{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509976939","data":{"timestamp":" 947509976939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfu_ne_me"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509983564","data":{"timestamp":" 947509983564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nge_me_va"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947509991142","data":{"timestamp":" 947509991141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nge_me_va"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510001556","data":{"timestamp":" 947510001555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nge_me_va"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510008165","data":{"timestamp":" 947510008164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_me_mpe_mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510014809","data":{"timestamp":" 947510014807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mvu_me_be"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510022302","data":{"timestamp":" 947510022302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mvu_me_be"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510028926","data":{"timestamp":" 947510028926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ngo_me_shu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510035568","data":{"timestamp":" 947510035567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_shi_me_fi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510042212","data":{"timestamp":" 947510042212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_su_va_me"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510049681","data":{"timestamp":" 947510049681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_su_va_me"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510056343","data":{"timestamp":" 947510056342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ti_me_mwu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510062981","data":{"timestamp":" 947510062981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_me_di_hi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510069624","data":{"timestamp":" 947510069624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mre_me_hu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510077545","data":{"timestamp":" 947510077544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mre_me_hu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510092889","data":{"timestamp":" 947510092888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 953e01ae-54d4-4984-951a-66c7e8455676"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mre_me_hu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510111099","data":{"timestamp":" 947510111099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_gha-vyo-me"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510116507","data":{"timestamp":" 947510116506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ya-me-mtu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510123554","data":{"timestamp":" 947510123554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_shi-mlu-me"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510128754","data":{"timestamp":" 947510128754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ge-nyu-me"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510134261","data":{"timestamp":" 947510134261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mdo-li-me"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510139313","data":{"timestamp":" 947510139312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_li-me-mwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510144225","data":{"timestamp":" 947510144225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ya-me-mlu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510164291","data":{"timestamp":" 947510164291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_te-mvu-me"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510170303","data":{"timestamp":" 947510170303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" d7de69f7-1be0-4ffc-b98e-ac0726eea073"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-pe-kwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510202697","data":{"timestamp":" 947510202697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510204754","data":{"timestamp":" 947510204753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510206362","data":{"timestamp":" 947510206361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" ME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510208644","data":{"timestamp":" 947510208644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" ME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510210245","data":{"timestamp":" 947510210244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" MI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510212300","data":{"timestamp":" 947510212299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" MI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510213901","data":{"timestamp":" 947510213900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MO"," userResponse":" MO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510216039","data":{"timestamp":" 947510216038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MO"," userResponse":" MO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510217644","data":{"timestamp":" 947510217643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510219784","data":{"timestamp":" 947510219783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510221808","data":{"timestamp":" 947510221806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510221939","data":{"timestamp":" 947510221938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 1346cf20-97c8-425a-a9c4-a1cc85a954ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510246720","data":{"timestamp":" 947510246719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510247798","data":{"timestamp":" 947510247797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510250644","data":{"timestamp":" 947510250643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510251710","data":{"timestamp":" 947510251709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" ME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510254947","data":{"timestamp":" 947510254946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" MI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510256013","data":{"timestamp":" 947510256013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" MI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510259271","data":{"timestamp":" 947510259270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MO"," userResponse":" MO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510260334","data":{"timestamp":" 947510260333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MO"," userResponse":" MO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510262911","data":{"timestamp":" 947510262911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510262991","data":{"timestamp":" 947510262991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510265005","data":{"timestamp":" 947510265004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510265102","data":{"timestamp":" 947510265102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 76c0e6b9-0c66-4bf1-8394-684235d4674f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510289204","data":{"timestamp":" 947510289204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510295786","data":{"timestamp":" 947510295786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510300227","data":{"timestamp":" 947510300227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510305317","data":{"timestamp":" 947510305317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510310116","data":{"timestamp":" 947510310116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510315325","data":{"timestamp":" 947510315325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510320918","data":{"timestamp":" 947510320918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510328652","data":{"timestamp":" 947510328652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510337323","data":{"timestamp":" 947510337323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510342670","data":{"timestamp":" 947510342670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510348431","data":{"timestamp":" 947510348430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" e8910960-9852-45d7-803f-bbe022f5b037"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510366504","data":{"timestamp":" 947510366504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510371169","data":{"timestamp":" 947510371169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510375672","data":{"timestamp":" 947510375672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510380398","data":{"timestamp":" 947510380398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510385876","data":{"timestamp":" 947510385875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510391786","data":{"timestamp":" 947510391786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510396111","data":{"timestamp":" 947510396111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510400640","data":{"timestamp":" 947510400639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510404820","data":{"timestamp":" 947510404820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510412635","data":{"timestamp":" 947510412635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510418407","data":{"timestamp":" 947510418405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 554cf3a9-1d65-4192-a941-3aeaca39f920"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510440025","data":{"timestamp":" 947510440024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510440417","data":{"timestamp":" 947510440417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510440662","data":{"timestamp":" 947510440661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510440988","data":{"timestamp":" 947510440987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510441234","data":{"timestamp":" 947510441233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510444716","data":{"timestamp":" 947510444715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510445022","data":{"timestamp":" 947510445021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510445939","data":{"timestamp":" 947510445938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510446372","data":{"timestamp":" 947510446371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510449357","data":{"timestamp":" 947510449356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510449651","data":{"timestamp":" 947510449650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510450507","data":{"timestamp":" 947510450507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510451186","data":{"timestamp":" 947510451185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510451938","data":{"timestamp":" 947510451938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510452277","data":{"timestamp":" 947510452276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510452567","data":{"timestamp":" 947510452566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510452895","data":{"timestamp":" 947510452894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510453172","data":{"timestamp":" 947510453171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510456820","data":{"timestamp":" 947510456819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510457214","data":{"timestamp":" 947510457213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510457458","data":{"timestamp":" 947510457457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510457783","data":{"timestamp":" 947510457782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510458026","data":{"timestamp":" 947510458025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510461530","data":{"timestamp":" 947510461530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510461834","data":{"timestamp":" 947510461832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510462752","data":{"timestamp":" 947510462751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510463186","data":{"timestamp":" 947510463185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510466159","data":{"timestamp":" 947510466157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510466453","data":{"timestamp":" 947510466452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510467309","data":{"timestamp":" 947510467308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510467989","data":{"timestamp":" 947510467988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510468737","data":{"timestamp":" 947510468736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510469071","data":{"timestamp":" 947510469070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510469353","data":{"timestamp":" 947510469353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510469682","data":{"timestamp":" 947510469681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510469962","data":{"timestamp":" 947510469961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510473371","data":{"timestamp":" 947510473369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510473451","data":{"timestamp":" 947510473451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 5d2de45d-4e96-4973-b12c-223a5d2a7574"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510485537","data":{"timestamp":" 947510485537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_si-le-nya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510490311","data":{"timestamp":" 947510490310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_ha-si-ya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510494861","data":{"timestamp":" 947510494861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_si-nda-mlu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510499679","data":{"timestamp":" 947510499678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_twe-si-hi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510504383","data":{"timestamp":" 947510504383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_twe-mwe-si"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510509300","data":{"timestamp":" 947510509300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_nga-si-jo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510513929","data":{"timestamp":" 947510513928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_si-shu-si"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510519214","data":{"timestamp":" 947510519214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_te-si-ya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510524849","data":{"timestamp":" 947510524849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_mtu-mbo-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510531404","data":{"timestamp":" 947510531404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_si-vyo-wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510537199","data":{"timestamp":" 947510537198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 8e14dc39-b247-4538-9834-feb4b49d0ffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.show.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_si_si-vyo-wa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510560538","data":{"timestamp":" 947510560538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 70e812ca-36dc-409e-ae60-5d837c782d1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_si_fo-mcho-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510561174","data":{"timestamp":" 947510561173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" 70e812ca-36dc-409e-ae60-5d837c782d1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_si..si.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_si_fo-mcho-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510597807","data":{"timestamp":" 947510597807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_si_mche_te"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510604459","data":{"timestamp":" 947510604459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ng'o_si_nya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510611126","data":{"timestamp":" 947510611126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mte_kwe_si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510617761","data":{"timestamp":" 947510617761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yo_si_di"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510624401","data":{"timestamp":" 947510624400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nje_nge_si"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510631033","data":{"timestamp":" 947510631033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mu_si_mgu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510637651","data":{"timestamp":" 947510637651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_si_twi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510644255","data":{"timestamp":" 947510644255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_si_bu_mto"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510650875","data":{"timestamp":" 947510650873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mche_vo_si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947510655876","data":{"timestamp":" 947510655876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_161230"," gameId":" ae458079-d927-412f-bffc-045c236d2d30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.si..si.noShow..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mche_vo_si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}